<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="207639" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Welcome, hero!&lt;BR&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Valkyon Federation always tries its best to support its operatives, and has many benefits in store for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please keep up the good work.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;May the blessings of the goddess be upon you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;This note has no effect on XP gains or quest progression, and you may destroy it after reading it.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Skill Advancement: When characters reach Level 66, they start earning Skill Advancement XP to advance their skills.&lt;BR&gt;You can obtain Skill Advancement Tomes/Optimization Scrolls and Complete Skill Advancement Tomes/Optimization Scrolls through special events, the TERA Store, or through random item drops, and use them to optimize or advance your skills without having to spend Gold or materials. Skill Advancement Level is capped at 180.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Caution: Skill Advancement can't be unlocked unless you learn all available skills at their maximum levels.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Skill Advancement (Lv. 66, 68, 70)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Use Skill Advancement Tomes (I, II, or III) and Skill Advancement Points to advance your skills to level 60.&lt;BR&gt;Skill Advancement is highly recommended for your character’s growth because it gradually enhances your skills and grants additional stats.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Skill Optimization (Lv. 67, 69)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Use Skill Optimization Scrolls (I or II) and Gold to unlock new options (PvE or PvP) for a skill.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Source:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;[Dungeons]&lt;BR&gt;Velik's Sanctuary, Velik's Hold, Red Refuge, and RK-9 Kennel&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;[Exodor Daily Quests]&lt;BR&gt;Exodor Reputation, obtainable normally through Daily quests and additionally through other activities, can be used to buy Skill Optimization Scrolls.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Put away the note.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
