<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="40" huntingZoneId="56" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">(This letter has been scratched out and rewritten multiple times; clearly, the writer felt very conflicted.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, how’s everything since you killed my dearest Argog? Hard feelings aside, I need to talk to you. I can get you Odwin and Leander.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I don’t trust you entirely, but you are the only one who can help me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I don’t want to ask you a favor, but I cannot let them give the Red Raiders a bad name.&lt;BR&gt;Meet me at {@linkcreature:55#7821#Rendezvous Point}.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;— Hennika&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;[You must have equipment level 463 or higher to enter Grotto of Lost Souls.]</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">During the search for Leander, &lt;PCNAME&gt; sided with a former foe, Hennika, who asked &lt;PCNAME&gt; to capture Leander and Odwin.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When &lt;PCNAME&gt; found Leander, the high elf was summonning a demon. &lt;PCNAME&gt; destroyed the portal generator and stops the ritual. Frustrated by the failure of his plan, Odwin reverts to his true form: that ofthe dragon, Kylos!&lt;BR&gt;After a brutal battle, &lt;PCNAME&gt; returned to Hennika. who offerend a pendant normally only given to high-ranking Red Raiders.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt; delivered the pendant to Launa and told her that Leander's plan failed.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="55" prevId="1" villagerId="7821">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">So, you're here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I really didn't want to ask you for help.&lt;BR&gt;Poor Argog, so cruelly butchered...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But I'm no fool. I cannot handle Odwin and Leander by myself. It's all I can do to stay one step ahead of the federation.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If anyone can stop them, it's you.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I am listening."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Leander went completely nuts after this Odwin fellow started working with him.&lt;BR&gt;I felt betrayed, because he no longer acts like a true Red Raider.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You understand?&lt;BR&gt;Argog lived for the Red Raiders. And he died for the Red Raiders.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I cannot let Odwin and Leander defile Argog's good name and reputation... or the Red Raiders'.&lt;BR&gt;I'm not the only one of us who feels this way.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You must help me defeat them.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I will."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Thanks.&lt;BR&gt;I know you have no reason to trust me, but you should do this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Many of my comrades fell for Leander's promises... his lies.&lt;BR&gt;I have to stop the rest of them from making the same mistake.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, go to the {@LinkCreature:55#9782#Grotto of Lost Souls} and deal with Odwin and Leander.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="55" prevId="3" villagerId="7821">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Odwin is dead? What of Leander?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What happened to him?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"He slipped away."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Fair enough.&lt;BR&gt;I hope to see him come around, but I know that's not likely to happen.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Nevertheless, you've given the raiders a second chance.&lt;BR&gt;I was right to trust you.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"The feeling is mutual."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Don't think this erases what you did to Argog.&lt;BR&gt;But you should take this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Leander gave these pendants to the most high-ranking Red Raiders.&lt;BR&gt;Take it to the federation. They'll think of it as another token of your heroism.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I still can't forgive you, but I will never forget that you helped me.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="55" prevId="4" villagerId="7825">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;? Why are you here?&lt;BR&gt;Did you know that the Red Raiders hide here?&lt;BR&gt;Marvelous work! You were few steps ahead of me!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I took the tome to the federation. Translating it was a hassle, but it convinced them.&lt;BR&gt;Leander is now the official leader of the Red Raiders.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Do you recognize this pendant?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">I do.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Only worn by officers of the Red Raiders.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Did you get this from Leander?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Explain what happened in the Grotto of Lost Souls.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">It does not make sense. Why did Odwin not hold the ritual himself? He is far more powerful than Leander.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Is it because Leander is an expert on demonology?&lt;BR&gt;I have a bad feeling about this. I will investigate this matter.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Anyway, we killed Leander's puppet master.&lt;BR&gt;Leander should lay low for awhile.&lt;BR&gt;Thanks for acting so quickly.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
